{
    "subject": "resource/Summer_of_'42",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Summer of '42",
    "human_readable": "The name of the Summer of '42 is Summer of '42.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9492903351783752,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie Summer of '42?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8956232666969299,
            "question": "Is the title of the movie Summer of '42 also its storyline's setting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8489456176757812,
            "question": "Who are some of the main characters in Summer of '42?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.837851881980896,
            "question": "During which year does the story of Summer of '42 take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.824699878692627,
            "question": "Could you tell me more about the plot of Summer of '42?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7757211327552795,
            "question": "Where can I watch Summer of '42?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7712172865867615,
            "question": "Is Summer of '42 a popular movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6836869716644287,
            "question": "What genre does the movie Summer of '42 belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6675478219985962,
            "question": "Who directed the film Summer of '42?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6529891490936279,
            "question": "Has Summer of '42 won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of the Summer of '42 is Summer of '42.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5728_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the film Summer of '42?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5728_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does the movie Summer of '42 belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5728_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Summer of '42 a popular movie?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5728_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5728_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5728_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5728_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5728_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5728_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5728_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5728_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5728_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5728_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5728_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as the film's title is indeed mentioned and referred to as \"Summer of \u201942\" in various sections."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe document explicitly mentions \"Summer of \u201942\" as the title of the film, thus confirming that the name of the film is indeed \"Summer of '42\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}